Today is birthday If we celebrate it together,
Nothing could be more wonderful. You said…
You've been through a lot until today
You’ve overcame this far,
You are the best
Any feelings in the bottom of my heart
You taught me some day
HAPPY BIRTHDAY
Leave a lot of memories with you
I’m unreliable, but I do my best reliably
HAPPY BIRTHDAY
Leave a lot of memories with you
I’m unreliable, but stay together
I make you smile
Today is birthday If we celebrate it together,
Nothing could be more wonderful. You said it but..
Thinking about things until today,
I should probably have prepared a trophy for you as my special prize
This one thing is true
Your one word,
it saves the world
HAPPY BIRTHDAY
Leave a lot of memories with you
1 minute, 1 second, Take it all without missing
HAPPY BIRTHDAY
Leave a lot of memories with you
Proof of you and your smile that I want to save,
and the Behind the Scenes
Even if your light disappears,
The day will come that you can think you are alright
HAPPY BIRTHDAY
Leave a lot of memories with you
I’m unreliable, but I keep do my best reliably
HAPPY BIRTHDAY
Leave a lot of memories with you
I’m unreliable but stay together
I make you smile